Jered McCullough

↑ 611 Mission St, San Francisco, CA 94105

+1 (707) 8459114

http://www.linkedin.com/in/jeredmccullough

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Ruby

Rails, Sinatra, Rspec

I have constructed several different webapps from the ground up using both Sinatra and Rails as the server backend in concert with Postgres SQL

Javascript

Jquery, Backbone, Angular, Node.js, Express, Jasmine

I have used several different frameworks to build webapps, Node and Express the backend and several others on the frontend including Jquery, Backbone and Angular

Other

Matlab, SQL, Compass, Foundation, Bootstrap, Haml/Jade, Postgres, Mongo, Heroku, C++

I have experience using several other technologies, while at University I studied C++ and developed mathematical models using Matlab, while for most of my applications I have used both Foundation and Bootstrap for front end design.

EDUCATION

2013 HUMBOLDT STATE UNIVERSITY

MajorMATHEMATICSMinorSPANISH

2014 Makersquare

Course Software Engineering

Experience Abroad

Ecuador Student - 05/11 - 9/11 China Volunteer - 9/11 - 8/12

COMMUNITY SERVICE

FOOTBALL COACH SUMMER'S 2008/2009

Mad River Youth Football

Construction Worker July 2002 – July 2004

RCHDC

WORK EXPERIENCE

July 2014 - Present

Software Developer | Contract

Piper CRM

Created notification system and automatic contact imports utilizing Contexio API and developed an email parsing program to add contacts information automatically.

With a team of 3 developed and deployed a visually appealing user interface

Reviewed and refactored others code using Github for version control, as well as using daily standups and weekly sprints for status updates.

Used test driven and agile development practices for deployment and design.

We used Ruby on Rails with Postgres, for the backend and database, as well as Angular and Foundation for the front end

March 2013 - Jan 2014

Pharmacy Technician

Lima's Professional Pharmacy

Transcribed and filled pharmaceutical prescriptions in a fast paced environment

Worked in an office environment billing insurance

Aug 2012 - March 2013

Adv. Stats Calculus and Linear Algebra Tutor Humboldt State University Math Lab

Summer 2006 - Summer 2011

Technician

Computer Design and Repair

Designed, constructed and installed custom personal computers. Installed routers and modems networking both PCs and Macs. Upgraded and repaired old computers with new hardware. Installed new operating systems: Windows, Linux and Mac OSX. Provided personal one-on-one training for basic computer functions, such as e-mail, and training in programs like Microsoft Word/Excel/PowerPoint.